[
  { "question": "Who wrote 'Rebecca' (Last name)?", "answer": "DuMaurier" },
  { "question": "What genre is 'Rebecca'?", "answer": "Gothic" },
  { "question": "Where is 'Rebecca' set?", "answer": "Manderley" },
  { "question": "Who is the antagonist (Last name)?", "answer": "Danvers" },
  { "question": "Who was Maxim’s first wife (First name)?", "answer": "Rebecca" },
  { "question": "What period is 'Rebecca' from?", "answer": "1930s" },
  { "question": "What was Rebecca’s illness?", "answer": "Cancer" },
  { "question": "Who was Rebecca’s lover (Last name)?", "answer": "Favell" },
  { "question": "Who helps the narrator (Last name)?", "answer": "Crawley" },
  { "question": "What is Maxim’s dog’s name (First name)?", "answer": "Jasper" },
  { "question": "Who is the narrator’s employer (Last name)?", "answer": "VanHopper" },
  { "question": "What is the narrator afraid of?", "answer": "Rebecca" },
  { "question": "What does Mrs. Danvers idolize?", "answer": "Rebecca" },
  { "question": "Who is Rebecca’s cousin (Last name)?", "answer": "Favell" },
  { "question": "What is the white dress a symbol of?", "answer": "Rebecca" },
  { "question": "What kind of novel is 'Rebecca'?", "answer": "Mystery" },
  { "question": "Who is the first person the narrator falls in love with?", "answer": "Maxim" },
  { "question": "What is Rebecca’s nickname for Maxim?", "answer": "Max" },
  { "question": "What is the name of the manor the narrator and Maxim move to?", "answer": "Manderley" },
  { "question": "Who is the narrator’s maid?", "answer": "Frith" },
  { "question": "Who warns the narrator about Mrs. Danvers?", "answer": "Beatrice" },
  { "question": "Who does Maxim kill in the novel?", "answer": "Rebecca" },
  { "question": "Who does the narrator replace as the mistress of Manderley?", "answer": "Rebecca" },
  { "question": "Who is the character that reveals Rebecca’s secret to the narrator?", "answer": "Favell" },
  { "question": "What is Maxim’s family estate called?", "answer": "Manderley" }
]
